I asked Wonho to leave
before you come
I thought it'd be better
to talk in private
What did the
production team say?
At first, there was
a storm of protest
But later, it went viral
and the viewership
reached the highest
so they didn't protest
anymore
We only have a few more
episodes left anyway
Still, stay away from
that guy or Shin Yoo-il
Keep your head down
for a while
For how long?
Do whatever you want
with that friend
And Shin Yoo-il…
You'd better not
see him anymore
Ma'am
if there were
no scandal like that
would this not
have happened now?
No
That was the condition
in the first place
I'll go ahead
Wait
I'm sorry
You can stay
as long as you want
[Shindecent]
[Yoo-il…]